前情提要
previously on "the 100"...
这是命中注定的
this is how it was meant to be,
你和我并肩作战
you and me fighting side by side.
- 妈妈  救命  - 霍普
- mommy, please help! -hope.
救命
help!
乔丹
jordan?
根据我们的调整协议
according to our adjustment protocol,
没有信仰的人必须被净化
nonbelievers must be purified.
放下武器  我们不想杀死他们
weapons down. we don't want to kill them, ok?
他们想杀了我们
they want to kill us.
欢迎回来  丹尼尔·普莱姆  凯莉·普莱姆
welcome back daniel prime and kaylee prime.
背叛朋友并不是答案
betraying your friends is not the answer.
你只复活了5个普莱姆
you've only resurrected 5 primes.
我们要的宿主都齐了
we have all the hosts we need.
艾比  抱歉不得不这样做
i'm sorry it has to be this way, abby.
- 别这样  - 不  放开她
- don't do this! - no. leave her alone!
- 不  - 不
- noooo! -no!
- 妈妈  - 亲爱的
- mom?  - oh, sweetheart.
我们要救我们的人
we're gonna save our people.
我为你感到自豪  墨菲
i'm proud of you, murphy.
约瑟芬叫我约翰
josephine called me john.
把她扔给狼群
throw her to the wolves.
不  我在克拉克的思维中看见过她
no. i saw her in clarke's mind.
我们需要她一起上飞船
we need her to get on that ship.
克拉克  艾比  你们做什么
clarke, abby, what re you doing?
那不是克拉克和艾比
that's not clarke and abby.
很好  尽管我听说了你们对凯恩做的事
very good. seems we got our nightblood
不过似乎我们还是得到了夜血
despite what i'm told you did with kane.
现在你们有3秒钟的时间滚开
now you have 3 seconds to stand down.
否则呢  要是你杀了他们
or what? if you kill them,
我们就杀了你
we kill you.
你没想过这点
you didn't think this through.
1...
2...
放下武器
weapons down now.
说过了
told you.
克拉克的记忆也许很恶心
clarke's memories may suck,
但确实能派上用场
but they do come in handy.
走  快走
move. move.
因陀罗  怎么回事
indra, what is this?
都冷静点
just say calm.
你们又醒了多少人
how many more of you are awake?
- 没有  - 你确定吗
- none.  - are you sure?
我们会扫荡这艘船
we'll sweep the ship.
杀死看到的所有人
anyone we find dies,
如果找到一个  你们这也得死一个
and for each of them, so does one of you.
你要修改之前的答案吗
care to amend your answer?
没有
no.
你是他们的领袖
ok. you're their leader,
现在的情况是这样
so here's the situation.
我们要驶向贝塔星
we're setting sail for planet beta.
有20年的行程
it's a 20-year journey.
你们能戴上镣铐  和我们一起和平得躺在低温舱里
you can take it with us peacefully in cryo...
去救玛蒂  剩下的人我来
save madi. i'll take care of the rest.
或者今天就是你们的死期
or you can die today.
我们给你们一小时来决定
we'll give you an hour to decide.
进攻
在这里除了我们没有人能发号施令
no one gives orders here but us.
让他们烂在这吧
let them rot.
来吧  我们还有事情要讨论
come on. we have things to discuss.
把门锁起来
lock it up.
退后
stay back.
瑞文
raven.
终于
finally.
楼上的医务室有台电脑
there's a computer upstairs in med bay.
跟我来
follow me.
盖娅
gaia...
解释一下
explain.
那样的忠诚很危险
devotion like that is dangerous.
尽管他们知道会死  还是会服从她的命令
they obeyed her even though they knew they would die.
等等  贝塔星球
just wait. planet beta--
拉塞尔  我们甚至都不知道那能不能生存
russell, we don't even know if it's survivable.
要是不行  我们就去伽马星
if it isn't, we go for gamma,
beta，gamma，delta，epsilon是希腊字母2，3，4，5的意思
不行就去德尔塔  再不行就艾普斯龙
then delta, then epsilon.
我们甚至不需要登陆  就能确定它是否适合生存
we won't even have to land to find out if it's survivable.
假设那里没有信号异常
assuming there are no other signal-sucking anomalies,
我们可以从这里
we can access the mind drives
无线接入其他团队的思维驱动器
of the other teams wirelessly from up here.
我们曾经都是探险家  对吧
come on. we were explorers once, weren't we?
拉塞尔  我爱你
russell, i love you,
我会和你一起穿越星辰
and i will go with you across the stars and back,
你说的对
but you're right.
那孩子是个问题
that child is a problem.
天哪  她有夜血
oh, for god's sake, she has the blood.
事实上  我选中她做我的下一任宿主
in fact, dibs on her as my next host.
西蒙妮  要是我们杀了他们的领袖
simone, if we kill their leader,
他们就不可能追随我们了
they will never follow us,
我们需要这些人来做奴仆
and we need those people to serve us
除非你想自己打扫厕所
unless you plan on cleaning latrines.
好吧  那我们就杀了她的沉睡大军
fine. then we kill her sleeping army
我保证他们已经在谈论
because i promise you they are already talking
要如何唤醒这些人了
about how to wake them.
我们带了足够的思维清除剂
we brought enough mind-wiping fluid
能在他们睡着的时候一锅端
to erase them all in their sleep,
在我们中有人需要新宿主之前
where they'll be perfectly preserved
他们会被完好得保存在那
until one of us needs a new host.
我们甚至都不需要认识他们
we'll never even have to know them.
好吧  但之后就要去贝塔星  同意吗
fine, but then it's on to beta. agreed?
小约  你怎么说
josie, what say you?
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
开什么玩笑  这很聪明啊
heh. are you kidding? it's brilliant.
一点点的种族灭绝  能让我们睡个好觉
a little genocide, a long nap.
这有什么的  我们去探险吧
what the hell? let's be explorers.
地 球 百 子
第六季        第13集
翻译： 噬魂师
翻译： 岛岛
翻译：兔兔秃了
翻译： Asteroid
校对： 噬魂
时间轴/特效：小螺号
统筹：Kate
总监：麦斯
这还要持续多久
how much longer will this last?
在这些墙塌掉之前估计好不了
it'll last longer than these walls will.
我们一起走
ok. we move together,
朝四面八方开火
firing all directions.
一到楼梯那  我们就逃进树林
once we get to the stairs, we haul ass to the woods.
不可能  我们不会丢下我们的人
no way. we're not leaving our people.
他们进来  就敲晕他们
here they come. knock them out,
把他们绑起来
we tie them up.
等他们发泄够了
take out enough,
最后就好了
eventually they'll stop.
结束了吗
is it over?
今天  我们净化圣所
today, we purify sanctum.
调整人  去找那些没有信仰的人
adjusters, go forth and find the nonbelievers.
把他们带到这  要是他们反抗
bring them here. if they resist,
格杀勿论
you may take their lives.
很好  你们都醒了
good. you're all awake.
开始吧
let's begin.
你相不相信
do you or do you not believe
普莱姆一族是神
in the divinity of the primes?
你们不需要药剂就能知道我的答案  女巫
you don't need a potion to find out my truth, witch.
普莱姆一族不是神  是骗子
primes are not gods. they are liars
还是杀人犯
and murderers.
你们没必要这样的
you don't have to do this.
我们不是你们的敌人
we're not your enemy.
不  你们是疾病
no. you're a disease,
而这就是治愈的方法
and this is the cure.
你们的血或是圣所的血
your blood or the blood of sanctum.
很好
good.
祝福丹尼尔  祝福凯莉
blessed is daniel. blessed is kaylee.
这是什么意思
what is the meaning of this?
祝福丹尼尔  祝福凯莉
blessed is daniel. blessed is kaylee.
祝福普莱姆一族
blessed are the primes.
平身
rise...
亲自解释下
and explain yourself.
我们是在听从拉塞尔·普莱姆的吩咐
we are purifying sanctum, holiness,
净化圣所  神圣的普莱姆
as so ordered by russell prime,
愿他的名为圣
hallowed be his name.
拉塞尔不在这里
russell is not here.
他抛弃了你们  而我们没有
he abandoned you! we did not.
调整协议是针对我们族群的
adjustments are for our flock.
地球人为什么也在
why are the earth people here?
算了
you know what? never mind.
没事
it's all right,
但我们该决定下怎么对待他们
but we shall decide what do with them.
把他们带去宫殿吧
let's take them to the palace.
帮他们站起来
help them to their feet.
- 听到了吧  - 走了
- you heard her.   - let's go.
让他们站起来
get them on their feet.
我们会护送你们过去的
we'll escort your holinesses.
不需要
that won't be necessary.
你们还有重要的事情要做
you've got important work to do.
他不行  加百列的孩子留在这里
not him. the child of gabriel stays.
多亏了普莱姆家族  我好想你
thank the primes. i missed you.
真是  有意思啊
that was... interesting.
不然下次再亲吧
another time perhaps.
他不记得我了
he didn't remember me.
看看现在谁是英雄啊
well, who's the hero now?
- 快走  - 其他人都去哪了
- come on.  - where's everyone else?
新氧
医美
专业医美APP
因为严谨  所以专业
新氧
医美
■
双眼皮
○
-
太空  现在只有乔丹在这里了
space. there's only jordan here now.
他是我们的下一站
he's our next stop.
别抬头看  冷静的走过去
just keep your eyes down and move calmly.
这些人还是有点不正常呢
these people are still whacked out of their minds.
他们为什么觉得你们是普莱姆一族
why do they think you're primes?
- 看看啊  - 是毒素
- uh, guys. - it's the toxin.
得赶快带他们去宫殿
we just have to get him to the palace.
加百利在等着  他会知道怎么办的
gabriel's waiting. he'll know what to do.
地球人  都怪他们
the earth people! it's their fault
拉塞尔才离开了我们
russell left us!
杀了他们
kill them!
跑  跑去宫殿
run! run get to the palace!
杀了他们  杀了他们
kill them! kill them!
加百利  开门
gabriel, open the door!
快点  快点
go, go, go, go!
我的人呢
my people?
我们尽力了
we got who we could.
快进去  赶紧
get inside. let's go.
我不敢相信我居然在说这个
i can't believe i'm saying this,
但是  我们确定吗
but...are we sure?
毕竟人类就只剩那么多了
i mean, it is the rest of the human race after all.
你说这话跟你父亲一模一样
simone: you sound like your father.
这比埃利吉乌斯3号上的睡眠池要大
well, it's bigger than the tank on eligius 3,
但这就是思维清除剂要去的地方
but this is where it goes.
- 把药剂给我  - 等一下
- hand me the serum.  - just wait.
你感觉还好吗  你脸色好苍白
are you feeling ok? you look pale.
你有没有流鼻血
have you had any nosebleeds
或者陌生的记忆片段
or memory flashes that aren't familiar?
没  你在说什么啊
no. what are you talking about?
就是我在克拉克的思想里看到的
oh, it's something i saw in clarke's mindspace.
她妈妈跟她的症状是一样的
her mother had the same neuromesh as she did.
我以为他们用电磁脉冲毁掉了  但是
i thought they destroyed it with an emp, but--
确实  复活前我给她检查过了
they did. i examined her before resurrection.
我可不想再犯一样的错误了
i wasn't about to make the same mistake twice.
约瑟芬
josephine...
给我
give it to me.
不
no.
不  你不是小约
no. not josie.
我不能让你们杀死这些人
i can't let you kill these people.
不管你们信不信  我对你们失去的真的很遗憾
believe it or not, i am sorry for your loss.
亲爱的  听我说
darling, listen to me.
我去叫其他人  追踪克拉克的大脑驱动
i'll get the others and track clarke's mind drive.
你去找那孩子
you get the child.
我们用她当筹码
we are gonna use her as leverage.
好  第二个硬盘也放入了
all right. second hard drive's jacked in.
你在哪学的这么编程
whoa. where'd you learn to code like that?
光明之城社区学院
city of light community college.
瑞文  集中注意力
raven, focus, please.
我看到过他一次  暗黑指挥官
indra: i saw him once--sheidheda.
他掌权的时候  我还是个小女孩
i was only a girl when he took trikru.
他从一个村子到另一个村子
he went from village to village,
屠杀所有不愿意下跪屈服的人们
butchering anyone who refused to kneel,
家人也一并处死
their families, too.
我们不能让这个生物控制同一族人
we cannot let this creature command wonkru.
我知道的  母亲
i know, mother.
如果我们失败了  我会杀了她的
if we fail, i'll take her life.
那不如我们不失败好不好
then how about we don't fail?
多亏了贝卡的笔记
thanks to becca's book,
我们绕过了人工智能安保机制
we're past the a.i.'s security.
如果我是对的 可以将其他指挥官的思维
if i'm right and it quarantined the minds
全部隔离开  那就应该可以很轻易的
of the other commanders, it should be easy
将暗黑指挥官隔离出来  扔到第二个电脑里去
to isolate sheidheda and dump it onto the second computer.
然后再杀掉这个王八蛋
in there, we kill the son of a bitch.
怎么了  出什么事了
what is it? what's wrong?
这好像是一个删除代码啊
it looks like there's a kill code,
但贝卡在笔记里没提到啊
but becca doesn't mention that in her notes.
那你到底能不能杀掉他
so can you kill it or not?
我可以  但是
i can, but...
也会毁掉火焰的
it'll destroy the flame.
他在逼我们做选择
he's making us choose.
她醒了
guys, she's waking up.
放开我
release me! ugh!
盖娅  你想让我怎么做
gaia, what do you want me to do?
杀了这个王八蛋
kill the son of a bitch.
乐意至极
with pleasure.
我会杀了你  赛达
i will kill you, seda!
我会杀了你们所有人
i will kill you all!
不用再屈服了
no more kneeling.
你们都会死的
you will all burn!
- 让开  - 孩子在哪里
- out of the way!  - where's the child?
瑞文
raven.
在那里  快点
in there! move, move.
马上就好了
we're almost there.
谁敢动就开枪
if anyone moves, shoot them, too.
下载错误
这孩子要跟我来
the child comes with me.
她停下了  我们很近了
she stopped. we're close.
别动
don't move!
不要再过来了
that's far enough.
我已经设置好了  我拉下这个
i set the inner door to stay open
内门就会开启
when i pull this,
要么把枪放下
so you can put the guns down,
要么就飘走吧
or you can float.
你们听到了
you heard her.
立刻放下武器
weapons down now.
妈妈
mom?
是我
yes. it's me.
西蒙妮  你在干什么
simone, what are you doing?
好  我们合作
ok, ok. we're doing it.
克拉克  我一直在假装
clarke, i've been pretending, too.
现在把他们锁起来  去救麦迪吧
now let's lock them up and go save madi.
别动  手放在我能看到的地方
don't move. keep your hands where i can see them.
我父亲叫什么
what's my father's name?
把嘴套拿下来  让她过来点
take off her gag and bring her closer.
我要让克拉克听到
i want clarke to hear this.
我想这意味着那婊子还活着
i take it that means the bitch is still alive.
你觉得她夺走了属于你的一切
you think she took everything from you,
但你还有你的生活
but you have your life,
有你的王国
you have your kingdom.
这两者我都可以帮你救回来
i can save both of those for you.
我只想要复仇
what i want is revenge!
如果你杀了她  她会为玛蒂难过
she'll grieve for madi if you kill her.
没错  但是那孩子
it's true, but since the child
已经不在了
is already gone,
你又能实现些什么呢
what are you really accomplishing?
我能给你的复仇
the revenge i can offer
要比你的痛快得多
will be so much sweeter.
你到底是谁
who the hell are you?
是时候了
you're there now.
圣所的夜血要起作用了
let the blood of sanctum do its work.
感受脸上的血气
feel the red sun on your face.
普莱姆家族会保护你
know that the primes will protect you,
普莱娅会保护你
that priya will protect you
前提是你相信
but only if you believe.
乔丹
jordan...
你相信神吗
do you believe in the divinity--
他在这
he's here!
人全了  任务完成了
that's everyone. mission accomplished.
乔丹  我们来了  你是安全的
jordan, we're here. you're safe.
把他放下来
lay him down.
他要修养一段时间
he'll be out for hours.
乔丹
jordan?
他陷入了回应的深渊中
he's in to deep to respond.
- 调整协议吗  - 恩
-adjustment protocol? -uh-huh.
圣所的夜血是真的吗
the blood of sanctum is real blood?
只有一部分是  西蒙妮预言
only partially. simone predicted
放血会加深
that the bloodletting would deepen
宗教体验
the religious experience,
但影响精神的成分是
but the psychoactive component is
赤日毒素
is pure red sun toxin.
- 有用的东西  - 如果使用得当
- useful stuff. - when used properly,
它确实可以
it can be, yeah.
救命
help!
看来我们找到调整者了
looks like we found the adjuster.
我不明白你的意思
i don't understand.
我们告诉他们真相
we told them the truth.
为什么他们还这么做
why are they still doing this?
如果他们接受事实
if they accept the truth,
他们的生命毫无意义
their lives mean nothing.
这就是我烧毁农场的原因
it's why i burnt the farm.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
帮我把他绑起来
help me tie him up.
我们可以用它来救酒馆里的人
we can use that to save the people in the tavern.
认知失调
cognitive dissonance.
他们会相信任何事情
they'll believe anything if it reinforces
只要他们想那是真的
what they want to be true,
即使你还是丹尼尔·李
even that you're still daniel lee.
还是抗毒血清吗  为什么
antitoxin again? why?
圣所的夜血比拉塞尔炸弹里的
the blood of sanctum is for more potent
更有威力
than what was in russell's bomb.
你把我当做囚犯
you take me in as a prisoner.
一旦我们进了酒馆
then once we're inside the tavern--
什么  不  不   不  不  等等
what? no, no, no, no. slow down.
我不可能喝那种东西
no way am i drinking that stuff.
他们在杀害非信徒
they're killing nonbelievers.
我的朋友就是其中之一
my friend who you left behind is one of them.
听着  很抱歉  但我们留下来是为了救我们的朋友
look. i am sorry, but we stayed to save our friends,
我们做到了
and we did that.
我们都在这
we're all here.
如果我能在太空中帮助我们的人民  我会的
if i could help our people in space, i would,
但这不是我们的战斗
but this isn't our fight.
好吧
ok.
等等我
wait for me.
我不能让这些人死  贝拉米
i can't let these people die, bell.
并肩作战
side by side.
就像命中注定的那样
like it was meant to be.
我想是时候做得更好了
i guess it's time to do better.
凯莉·普莱姆随时为你们服务
kaylee prime at your service.
- 埃默里  - 约翰  没关系
-emori. - john, it's ok.
有人需要留下来照顾米勒和乔丹
someone needs to stay behind and look after miller and jordan.
抱歉  打断一下
excuse me. sorry.
凯莉反对调整协议
kaylee was against the adjustment protocol.
所以当你把他们都带走的时候  他们才会相信
it's why they believed it when you took them all away.
一定要是丹尼尔
it has to be daniel.
好吧  但如果我死了  你要把我带回来
fine, but if i die, you're bringing me back.
不  我不会
no, i'm not.
好歹骗骗我啊
at least lie to me.
做一个神应该比这更有趣
being a god should be more fun than this.
我们需要把那扇门打开  瑞文
we need that door open, raven.
我在努力
working on it.
事实上  我现在对埃吉利乌斯的能力很恼火
i'm actually annoyed at eligius' competence right now.
这不是我干的
it wasn't me.
克拉克  你怎么  你怎么
clarke, how--how did you--
用肖恩的故障安全代码
shaw's failsafe code.
玛蒂在哪
where's madi?
拉塞尔  拉塞尔把她带走了
russell-- russell took her.
哦  不  不  不
oh, no. oh, no. no, no.
我们会把她救回来的
we'll get her back.
不  你不明白
no. you don't understand.
我杀了他的家人
i killed his family,
现在他要杀我的
and now he's gonna kill mine.
我不会让那事发生的
i won't let that happen.
恶魔唤醒了同一族
the demon awoke wonkru.
安静
想活命就跪下
树之国度的莱克萨说你很坚强
lexa from trikru said you were strong,
但你和她一样软弱
but you're as weak as her.
你的爱让你变成这样
your love has made you so.
有枪
gun!
别动
hold.
玛蒂
madi.
玛蒂  我知道你在里面
madi, i know you're in there.
请回到我身边
please come back to me.
我今天失去了我的母亲
i lost my mother today.
我不能也失去你
i can't lose you, too.
求求你了
oh, please.
我会扣动扳机
i'm gonna pull the trigger...
in 3...
2...
把普莱姆和他的人抓起来
放下武器
weapons down!
新氧
医美
专业医美APP
因为严谨  所以专业
新氧
医美
■
双眼皮
○
-
- 玛蒂  - 她在争夺身体的控制权
-madi? -she's seizing.
带她上楼
get her upstairs!
- 玛蒂  -快点
- madi? -hurry!
我们就快统治一切了
我们想象中的世界就要诞生了
一个新的完美世界
相反  你的软弱
灭杀了我们两
扶稳她
hold her steady.
玛蒂  玛蒂  我在这
madi, madi, i'm here.
听我的声音  你能做到的
listen to my voice. you can do this.
你必须战斗  玛蒂
you have to fight, madi.
你必须战斗
you have to fight!
再来一次
once more with feeling.
文件下载中
找到他了
got him!
完成下载
信号丢失  发生致命错误
她怎么还不醒
why isn't she waking up?
她的脉搏太弱了
her pulse is too weak.
不  不  不  不
no, no, no, no.
等等  我知道这是什么
wait. i know what this is.
我们必须把它取出来
we have to take it out
就像你在电磁脉冲后对我做的那样
like you did with me after the emp.
我需要一个刀片
i need a blade.
镊子
forceps.
我会合上它
i'll close.
- 我在这  - 你没事了
- i'm here. - you're ok.
我不再是指挥官了
i'm not the commander anymore.
谢谢你
thank you.
艾比的事我很抱歉
i'm sorry about abby.
瑞文
raven.
文件上传中
完成上传
他去了哪里
where did he go?
女士们先生们
ladies and gentlemen,
欢迎来到今晚的活动
welcome to the main event of the evening,
这是恶魔加百列的自我调整
an adjustment for the demon gabriel himself.
放轻松  大个子
easy, big boy.
还有地方再坐一个吗
got room for one more?
这边走  圣者
right this way, holiness.
只要有人敲门
as soon as someone else knocks on that door,
他们会知道我们占据了酒馆
they'll know we took the tavern.
这就是我们的切入点
that's where we come in.
加百列和墨菲控制着内部
gabriel and murphy control the inside.
我们确保没有其他人进去
we make sure no one else gets inside.
如果那样的话  就是30对3
if that happens, it'll be 30 on 3.
我喜欢我们的机会
i like our chances.
森林醒了
the forest is awake.
葡萄藤刺穿你的皮肤
the vines pierce your skin.
蜂群正在吞噬你
the swarm is devouring you.
你感觉到了吗
do you feel it?
如果你愿意  普莱姆可以救你
the primes will save you if you let them.
泽夫  我们有一位特殊的客人
zev, we have a special guest.
有什么问题吗  阁下
is something wrong, your grace?
没事  赶紧把这件事了结吧
no. let's get this over with.
给我们两个血清  我也需要进行调整
dose us both. i need adjusting, too.
我的复生过程出了点问题
something went wrong with my resurrection.
我的记忆模糊了
my memory is shot.
为我的光辉荣耀
for the glory and grace of me.
你出了这种事  我很抱歉
i'm sorry this happened to you.
你的血还是圣所之血
your blood or the blood of sanctum.
在火中净化圣所
we purify sanctum through fire!
去拿燃料  浸入圣所
get the fuel! soak it down!
我们一起  将恶魔和
together, we send the demon
他的伪先知送入地狱
and his false prophet to hell!
放下火炬  后退
leave the torch and back away.
里面的都是你的人
those are your people in there.
帮我们救救他们
help us save them.
那正是我们要做的
that's what we're doing.
他的牺牲是对我们所有人的祝福
their sacrifice will be a blessing to us all.
我不会让你得逞的
echo: can't let you do that.
毒素在宿主身上起效很快
the toxin is quick in this host.
抱歉了
i'm sorry about this.
你确实是个不错的男人
you really do seem like a nice guy.
吻技也不错
good kisser, too.
我能对付这些人  去拿火炬
i got these guys! go for the torches!
不要让他们进酒馆
keep them away from the tavern!
你花了好久
took your time.
这家伙更难对付
my guy was tougher.
为普莱姆家族的
for the glory and the grace
光辉荣耀
of the primes!
厄科  检查一下其他人
echo, check on the others.
你没事吧
you ok?
里面一切都还好吗
everything ok in there?
好得很  我参加过的最棒的派对
yeah. best party ever.
炫我一脸啊
show-off.
至少有十几个人逃走了
counted at least a dozen runners.
留意酒馆四周
watch all sides of the tavern
以防他们回来
in case they come back.
你身上什么时候出现那个的
when did you get that?
什么
what? what is it?
能让我看看吗
may i?
你之前见过这个吗
have you seen that before?
纹身吗  没有
the tattoo? no.
但我已经花了150年
no, but i've been studying it
来研究它
for 150 years.
我们称它为异石
we call it the anomaly stone.
你肯定是在异象里弄上的
you must have gotten it on the other side.
嘿  还觉得自己
hey. still think you were gone
只去了几秒钟吗
for only a few seconds?
这真漂亮  但它代表了什么意思
it's beautiful, but what does it mean?
问得好
good question.
它代表着我必须回去了
it means i have to go back.
他们回来了
they're back.
别因为这个耽误你
don't let this delay you.
我们还是要离开
we're still leaving.
异象在等着
the anomaly awaits.
*for what could have been... *
我马上过来
i'm right behind you.
* the weight is heavy, tell the sender that... *
乔丹
jordan...
你还好吗
you ok?
看起来你度过了一个艰难的夜晚
look like you had a rough night.
我还不是最艰难的
not as rough as some.
走吧  他们从太空回来了
come on. they're back from space.
我看到飞船了  你去吧
i saw the ship. you go.
我打算帮忙善后
i'm gonna help clean up our mess.
嘿
hey...
他们说是你害死了普莱娅
they say you got priya killed.
* i know i'll see you on the other side... *
乔丹  是真相害死了普丽娅
jordan, the truth got priya killed.
真相  谁说那是真相
the truth? according to who?
圣所或许并不完美
i'm just saying sanctum wasn't perfect,
但是  在我们来之前
but these people had peace
这些人本拥有和平
before we got here.
你确定你没事吗
you sure you're ok?
我没事
fine. yeah.
* won't let go of me *
* reminding me that you're gone *
* and i'm the one that can't breathe *
* that can't breathe *
* i know i'll see you *
杰克森
jackson!
* on the other side *
* the other side *
* wait for me *
* in fields of gold *
* it's not the end... *
我听说了艾比的事
i heard about abby.
我想改变结局
i tried to do better.
我尽力了
i did,
然后  我失去了我的母亲
and then i lost my mom.
告诉我这一切是值得的
tell me it was worth it.
告诉我  这是值得的
tell--tell me it was worth it.
嘿  嘿   我们确实改变了结局
hey, hey. we did. we did do better.
我必须相信这很重要
i have to believe that that matters.
* i know i'll see you *
* i know i'll see you on the other side *
* the other side *
我不得不说
i have to tell you
我确实非常兴奋
i'm very excited about this.
自从我们找到那块石头
i've been studying those symbols
我一直在研究上面的符号
since we found the stone.
也因为它  我们在这里建起了营地
we built the camp here because of it.
那个纹身
the tattoo.
这玩意已经有上千年的历史了
it's thousands years old.
我们不知道是谁建造了它
we have no idea who made it
也不知道是什么产生了让它浮起的电磁场
or what generates the magnetic field that holds it up,
但可以肯定的是  就是它吸收了所有无线电信号
but we're pretty sure it's what sucks in all the radio signals.
她背后的符号  有一些是红色的
echo: some of the symbols on her back are red.
是密码
it's a code.
很好  我们很快就能破解出它是做什么的
very good. we're about to find out what it's for.
能让我看看那个图案吗
may i see the drawing, please?
揭晓真相的时刻
moment of truth.
如果你是对的  会发生什么
what happens if you're right?
这个问题  我拟算出的结果写满了100本笔记
i filled 100 notebooks with possible answers to that question.
这个序列的最后一个符号
the last symbol in the series
被称为八元数
is called an octonion.
是一种远超出我运算水平的高等数学
advanced mathematics way above my head,
但我不认为你们的名字相同只是一个巧合
but i don't think it's a coincidence you share a name.
请  应该你来
please. it should be you.
不  不  不  不
no, no, no, no, no.
这不可能
it can 't be right.
让我再看一眼那个纹身
let me see the tattoo again.
肯定哪里搞错了
must have got something wrong.
安静
quiet.
我的天
oh, my god.
我就知道
i knew it.
这他妈是什么
what the hell is this?
她在这里
she's here.
迪约扎
diyoza?
霍普
hope?
我出不来
i couldn't get out of it.
他抓走了我的妈妈
he has my mother.
我很抱歉  奥克塔维亚
i'm so sorry, octavia.
奥克塔维亚  怎么回事
octavia, what's happening?
勇敢点  告诉他一切完成了
be brave. tell him it's done.
- 刀  - 不   不
- knife!  - no! no!
奥克塔维亚
octavia!
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
对字幕有任何意见和建议的同学请加Q群：544487177